All right, y'all, I got to tell y'all something.
When you're doing a job interview, either show up to be there or don't show up at all.
Because I just can't understand why some of y'all come on these interviews and act as if you're doing somebody a favor by showing up.
I had to interview somebody tonight and they came on the interview with this posture.
Okay.
And I said, do you know we can see you?
And their response was, yeah.
Do you not want to see me?
Baby, that's the end of the interview.
That's the end of the interview because if this is how we starting, baby, we not going no further.
And I think that a lot of people don't understand that at the end of the day, first impressions really do matter.
Come on to the interview with enthusiasm and a disposition that says, I want to be here.
It doesn't mean that you got to lick anybody's boobs.
It doesn't mean you got to kiss anybody's ass.
But you best represent yourself in the best way possible if this is the thing you want to do.
Ba-dum-dum.
Like my shirt?